[{"answer": "It's absolutely surreal.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "It must be a rather surreal atmosphere, isn't it?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "I wish I could tell you more about how the police evicted protesters from here, but I can't, because our cameras and most journalists' cameras were not allowed in here for hours and hours.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "What can you tell me about both those things?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "I think that's an outstanding question to be absolutely fair.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Has it galvanized them to, perhaps, be even more protesting down there in bigger numbers?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Well, it was predictable that, eventually, this would come to a head.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "John Timoney, what is your reaction to what's been going on in this park for the last 24 hours?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "I was there in 1951.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "When were you at Penn State?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "I have not spoken to him.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Have you spoken to him?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "I'd just say I pray that the Lord will bless you and the Lord will keep you and the Lord will bless all of those people that are around you and help you all stand strong and learn that God does forgive wrong things.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "What would you say if you got the chance?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "I think it was as big a shock to us in one sense as it has been to everyone.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "When you first got wind of this, did you ever imagine it would become as big as this become?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Well, you know what was startling about watching that, I had the exact same reaction, Piers, to that moment.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "You know, when you are asked, are you sexually attracted to young boys and it takes you 17 seconds to answer, you're basically hanging yourself, aren't you?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Well, our reporter, Sara Gannon (ph), did a story last Friday.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "How much did that come into play and preventing people who were, otherwise, apparently, good people like Joe Paterno from going to the police about these terrible crimes?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Five-year break.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Mickey, how are you?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "The acting wasn't something I was having fun doing anymore or liked doing.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "I've always wondered, why would you -- in the middle of this dazzling film career, want to go and get beaten around the head?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "You've always loved boxing, haven't you?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "It went good.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "How did it go, the boxing?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "I never say could have, would have, should have.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "Did you ever think you could have been a proper contestant?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "You know what it was, I needed the discipline.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "But what does it give you, that feeling when you get into the ring?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I did the movie at a time when I still wasn't very bankable.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "And boy, was it the comeback movie?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "The guy did a really great job with the nose.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "You know, I always had trouble with wrapping my hands, because my hands would swell up.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Is that from the fighting?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "I imagine it's hellish.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "Did you imagine?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Well, I did it because I had some issues when I was very young with authority and with physical --", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "Why do you think you did it?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "It was terrible.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "In the wilderness years, when you were walking, say, into a store in Hollywood, a grocery store or something, what was the reality of that?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah, didn't you used to be.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "You actually hear that line?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "I'm not going to go there.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "What was the worst name?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "Well, Stallone helped me out.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Who were the guys, the other actors who really stuck by you?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Once.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Had you seen each other since?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "It's always nerve-racking.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "When you met up again this time, how did it go?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Well, the first time we saw each in over 20 years was last year or something.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "So when she first saw you again this time, was it affectionate?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "I have never been until in the last couple of years, kind of acknowledged it.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Are you proud of it, from an acting point of view?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "I don't have any desire to read it.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "What was your view of the book?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "No, but I -- I mean, it's fascinating.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Anyway, what's the next thing you want to talk about?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "No, I don't have to wonder.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Do you ever wonder about that?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "I think I'm feeling you, Mickey.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "You feel me?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "No, they're stronger than us.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "Do you understand them better?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "No, I'm -- not necessarily, no.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "Are an easier guy to go out with, to date, to be with?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "Listen, when I -- listen, just to get the second chance, they're letting me back in the door.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Is that the ultimate?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "Do you still feel that?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "It wasn't the drinking.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Do you still drink much?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "My anger.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "ORGAN: What was your problem?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "And does that still flare up?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "I would do it in a diplomatic way, you know.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Should I be feeling a little nervous here, Mickey?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "Now that he has seen your face, he knows.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "Does he know he butchered my mother?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "Yes, he did.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "He came out to your premier last week?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "You told me.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "Who told you?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "I have -- I like the way you say with your country.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "What do you make of what's happening with your country right now?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "I don't really have one, to be honest with you.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "What is going wrong with America?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Yes, I am.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "Are you learning a bit of diplomatic tact in your old age, Mickey?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "I'll let you read my mind.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "Do you think actors should spout off about politics?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "No, I didn't get engaged.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 656, "question": "There's a wild rumor you got engaged recently?", "qSentId": 655}, {"answer": "None of your business, Piers.", "docId": "111115pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "Are you with anyone in any serious way?", "qSentId": 657}]